Who the hell is this girl?!
Don't mind her.
She's just the maid.
[SCOFFS]
Smells like one too!
Daniel, dear...
Can you check up
on our suite?
[SIGHS] It's taking so long.
Okay.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I'll leave now.
Hey!
I'm not done with you yet!
I'm sorry, ma'am. I...
don't understand.
If you'll insult me, could you
please do it in English?
So I can answer back.
[SELENA SCOFFS] Oh.
The maid has some attitude.
[BRENDA] I noticed the way
you looked at Daniel.
You like him!
Don't you?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[WHISPERS] You're perfect
for each other.
What did you say?!
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC STINGS]
You bitch!
[HANNAH] Ma'am, please stop!
- Enough, please!
- [BRENDA GROANS]
- Oh, Brenda!
- [PANTING]
Are you okay?
I may be a maid!
But I am a maid...
of honor!
[CRYING]
Mom!
My nose!
Your supervisor
is gonna love this.
[SCREAMING, CRYING]